Um, where are we going?
To Tilty's place.
Tilty... You mean the eldest
daughter of Marquess Claret?
Yep.
I seem to recall that her inhumane
nature has caused repeated problems,
and that she's been locked up
in a separate building...
Yep. That's pretty much right.
Lady Tilty isn't, um... dangerous, is she?
Oh, yeah. She's super dangerous.
She is certainly unusual.
She is the princess's
research partner, after all.
In other words, she's the
same type as the princess.
The Magical Revolution
of the Reincarnated Princess and the Genius Young Lady
My lady, I've brought visitors for you.
Let them in.
It's been a long time.
Sure has!
And is that the beloved
daughter of Duke Magenta?
Yeah! She's my cute, sweet assistant!
My name is Euphyllia Magenta.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Lady Claret.
Call me Tilty. I hate formalities.
Your rank's higher than mine, anyway.
Right...
So why did you come meekly trailing along
with her if you're just going to be silent?
I wanted to get your advice
regarding this dragon magicite.
Wow, so this is what
I've heard so much about.
You want me to use this the next time
I synthesize magic medicine, then?
Actually, nope!
I want to test out a new technique with it!
You didn't come up with some
deranged idea again, did you?
No, no!
I was cursed by that dragon.
Actually, it might be more correct to say
it entrusted me with knowledge!
What did you say?!
What's this about a dragon's curse?
Give me more details! Right now!
There's that dark, creepy hobby of yours.
What is this all about?
Tilty is a curse specialist.
Lady Tilty studies curses,
meaning medical cases that can't
be cured with medicine or magic.
I-I see... But why...
Miss Anis didn't tell you
about my condition?
I believe she said that when you use magic,
you become unbalanced,
causing adverse effects
on your mental state.
Yes, and due to that...
Well, I've made some pretty big messes.
When a noble can't even use magic right,
what else can you call it but a curse?
So that made me lose all interest in magic,
and I decided to pursue medicine instead.
I see. Your own suffering has
made you want to help others.
That's a wonderful attitude!
There's nothing that admirable about Tilty!
She's just a weirdo who finds
pleasure in cracking curses!
I don't need that from a freak
who risks her life to study magic
when she can't even use it.
And?
What does Miss Anis the Freak
want me to do?
You're just as mad as ever, I see.
Um, would you mind showing me
those papers, as well?
The knowledge I got from the dragon
gave me the idea!
I could absorb the magicite's
power safely this way, right?
You really intend to take
this thing into yourself?
Yep!
What are we to do with you, Princess?
Well, it sounds interesting,
so I'm fine with it.
Miss Anis...
I understand.
But please, don't do anything dangerous.
Princess, you've just received
a message from the castle.
A message?
Yes. A summons from His Majesty.
You are to visit the castle tomorrow.
I-I-I didn't do anything!
Perhaps he caught wind of your
experiments with Lady Tilty?
You think he'll be angry?
Do you think he won't be angry?
I wanna run away!
If you do that, I believe it
will only anger him more.
Good point...
Well, here I am.
I, Anisphia, have come to—
Welcome, Anisphia.
M-Mother?! Why are you here?!
You're alive?!
Yes, I'm alive.
And do you even need to ask why?
With so many terrible incidents happening,
I can't comfortably focus on diplomatic work.
I just returned from abroad yesterday,
and it sounds as if you've been quite active.
After all these years,
is it time for your mother
to educate you again?
For now, just sit down.
O-Okay...
Oh, never mind.
We called you here today
to talk about Algard.
Huh? About Al?
Yes. We've finally collated
all of the information.
Hey, so Euphie really isn't to blame at all!
That's true, but it's just a bit strange.
All of the people who questioned Miss Cyan
are sympathetic toward her.
Sympathetic?
Yes. There are those who believe
some of the fault lies with Euphyllia.
Though it clearly does not,
if one considers the circumstances...
So I've decided to summon
Baron Cyan's daughter here
and hear what she has to say in person.
I'd like you to be present
at that time. Will you?
I'm definitely interested, but...
You may be an outlandishly wild daughter,
but that doesn't mean we don't trust you.
With your intuition
and your unique point of view,
you might notice something that we don't.
We'll be counting on you.
Okay.
So... they decided to hear
what Lady Lainie has to say,
but something seems kinda weird...
You mean how people sympathize with her?
I don't think it's that hard to believe.
Some stupid boys just wanted to show off
for a pretty damsel in distress.
And the head of the idiots
is that idiot prince.
Hey! He's still my brother, you know!
I mean, yeah, he is stupid... He is, but...
Apparently, some of the ladies
feel that way, too.
It's not just students at the academy,
but people at the castle, too.
Everyone who's talked to
Miss Lainie is the same way.
Isn't that crazy?
So everyone who interacts with her
ends up favoring her?
I might have an idea why that is.
Ooh! That's my dark-hearted curse nerd!
You want to be cursed to death?
Oh, sorry! I mean, great master of curses!
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
And what is your opinion, Master Tilty?
Strictly speaking, it's not
really a curse, but...
Ow! Ow! That stings!
Do that slower! Gentler! More carefully!
And? How did it go?
Oh, well... It seems like it's
exactly as Tilty and I thought.
Just to make sure, I talked to one of the
people who was condemning Euphie,
and he had no awareness of it at all.
I just need to see Miss Lainie in person
tomorrow for the final confirmation.
Come with me, Ilia.
I haven't the slightest idea
what's going on, but very well.
I will entrust everything to you.
Leave it to me! I've already
come up with a countermeasure.
And is this your countermeasure?
Yeah, well... it's more like
I figure that's how it'll turn out.
I see.
I will begin making
preparations for tomorrow.
Try not to stay in the bath too long.
I decided to condemn her
at Prince Algard's suggestion.
Seriously, what the heck are you doing, Al?
It suits you, Princess.
Yeah, thanks.
Miss Anis!
Euphie?
You look beautiful.
You don't have to flatter me.
I do wish I could accompany you,
but if I were there...
It's okay. Just look after the place for me.
Okay. I'll be awaiting your return.
Baron Cyan, and his daughter, Lainie.
Welcome.
Your Majesty! Please forgive my
daughter's horrendous insolence!
Be at ease, Lord Cyan.
I asked you here today in hope
of bringing the truth to light.
Just relax for now.
Yes, Your Majesty. Please forgive me.
I am deeply moved by your kindness.
Miss Lainie Cyan, raise your head.
If I may be direct, you and Algard
developed feelings for one another, correct?
No.
Most certainly not.
Such things are beyond my station,
and I have not even entertained the notion.
I would be lying if I said I did not
think favorably of Prince Algard,
but I would never dream of doing anything
that would cast a dark shroud
over the royal family's future.
I see. You certainly don't seem to be lying.
Indeed. There seems to be
no falsehood in her heart.
Perhaps there was some sort
of misunderstanding.
It is possible that Algard acted hastily.
It seems likely that there was a sad
misunderstanding on both sides.
It is clear that no blame
lies with Miss Cyan.
Yes! I swear to you that my
daughter meant no harm!
Hmm... That seems to be true.
I don't feel right...
You are absolutely unbelievable!
I-It's not like that, Father!
I, Anisphia, would like
to offer a suggestion!
I won't hear any excuses!
This is serious!
Speak, then.
Could you ask the others to leave?
What?
There's something I want
to ask Miss Lainie.
In the interest of protecting her dignity,
I'd like to ask it in front of
as few people as possible.
I see no problem with this.
Your Majesty, I trust Anis's intuition.
W-Wait! My daughter really
isn't planning anything!
Princess Anisphia, don't you think
asking us to leave is a bit hasty?
Lord Chartreuse.
Sending everyone away so you can
question a poor, delicate young lady?
Telling her not to be afraid
is expecting too much.
I understand what you're saying,
but this is something that
nobody but me can verify.
Verify what?
Are you saying you suspect
Miss Cyan of wrongdoing?
Do you object to what I've asked?
The princess is clearly insisting.
Should we not stand down, then?
I will allow it.
Anis and Miss Lainie may speak in private.
All present, leave for now.
Sorry to spring this on you.
I just want to check something about you.
Um, I really haven't done anything!
I'm sorry, but I need to verify this now,
or you may end up at a disadvantage.
No...
So the only answer you need
to give is "yes." Okay?
Yes...
Wh-What are you—
Quiet, now. I won't do anything to you.
Pardon me.
Okay, got it. All done.
Miss Lainie...
Wh-What is it?
Are you aware that you're using magic?
Huh?
Great, so you don't realize it?
This is a problem.
Huh? Um, I... I'm not using any magic...
I-I don't know what you're talking about!
I didn't do anything!
Yeah, I get it. I know you're
not doing it of your own will.
Miss Lainie, I'm pretty sure... I think...
that you're not an ordinary human.
N-Not an ordinary... human?
Listen to me calmly.
There's something in your heart
that I believe to be magicite.
M-Magicite? What? But how?
I'm... n-not human?
It's not that you're not human,
but you're sort of like me.
I've been researching magicite,
and as part of that,
I sort of took some into my body.
And that's how I can tell.
I think the magicite inside you seems to be
a type that affects people's minds.
To put it more simply,
I believe you have the power of fascination.
Fascination?
Yep.
Is that true?! Have I been
doing that all this time?!
Well, I don't know that much...
But I think it's highly probable.
People have always liked me,
but that caused others to be mean to me,
to betray me, to bully me...
It made me so scared,
I started trying to avoid being liked,
to stand out as little as possible.
Fascination, huh?
If not for the dragon's power,
I would've been in trouble, too.
I never would have imagined there
was someone with magicite in them.
And to think it gives her the
power of fascination...
Yes, but I can't say for sure
that she can control that power.
That's probably why it
activated indiscriminately
against people who were kind to her,
and why she began to experience
friction in her relationships.
That's...
Her power is dangerous.
It could threaten this entire nation.
We may have to...
There's no problem.
I have a countermeasure.
I will assume responsibility
and take Miss Lainie in.
Honestly... That's exactly
what's wrong with you!
Huh?
Keeping Miss Lainie at your villa
will cause major problems.
Problems?
Who are you living with right now?
Oh!
Episode Six
Getting to the Truth of the
Annulment and the Fascination
She is as unpredictable as ever.
I never expected her to get involved in this.
This means our plan is...
The plan remains unchanged,
but we may need to move faster.
I should have known she would be the one
to stand in my way in the end.
What do you intend to do?
She is a problem,
but she is not without flaws.
She has plenty of weaknesses
we can exploit.
Do that, then.
Mistakes will not be tolerated.
Yes, we can make no mistakes.
This is the end of it, after all.
Episode Seven
The Magic Lecture of the
Founder and the Assistant